

NICOLÁS BAUZÁ

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT



Phone

+598 96 103 064



Email

nicolasbauza21@gmail.com



Address

Arenal Grande 1615 Montevideo - Uruguay



EDUCATION

Escuela MilitarUruguay

2012 - 2015



- English
- Spanish



ABOUT ME

Hi! I'm Nicolas, and I'm looking for my first experience in the world of technology. I've been working in the army for 10 years, where I had the opportunity to lead teams of up to 40 people in different situations. Since I can remember I have always been fascinated by technology, I have always been curious about how things around me work, but I never imagined myself doing it, until one day I said to myself, why not? and here I am. Since that day there is no day that I don't look for new things to learn. I'm looking for a place to keep learning, and learning.



WORK EXPERIENCE

O Uruguayan Army

2012-2022

I worked as an Officer in the Uruguayan Army for 11 years, where I led human groups of up to 40 people.

O United Nations

2019-2020

I worked for the United Nations for 18 months in Africa where I had the opportunity to lead human groups and work with people from different countries for world peace.



MY SKILLS & EXPERTISE

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React.js

Node.js + Express

PostgreSQL

Material UI &

Bootstrap